{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865058398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865058398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" da73c3f1-0f57-4713-bf43-ce6f3f177ac5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865072881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865072881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" da73c3f1-0f57-4713-bf43-ce6f3f177ac5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865092973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865092972"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" da73c3f1-0f57-4713-bf43-ce6f3f177ac5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865093735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865093735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" da73c3f1-0f57-4713-bf43-ce6f3f177ac5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865108813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865108812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" da73c3f1-0f57-4713-bf43-ce6f3f177ac5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865119621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865119621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" da73c3f1-0f57-4713-bf43-ce6f3f177ac5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865120425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865120425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" da73c3f1-0f57-4713-bf43-ce6f3f177ac5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a_ne"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865131305","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865131304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" db5b1d52-2573-4e62-9d54-0b67cf8cad96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865136281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865136281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" db5b1d52-2573-4e62-9d54-0b67cf8cad96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865144734","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865144734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" db5b1d52-2573-4e62-9d54-0b67cf8cad96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865152992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865152992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" db5b1d52-2573-4e62-9d54-0b67cf8cad96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865158354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865158354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" db5b1d52-2573-4e62-9d54-0b67cf8cad96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865166103","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865166102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" db5b1d52-2573-4e62-9d54-0b67cf8cad96"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865183029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865183028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" e1624187-e9cc-4941-981e-a77a780e1b9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865183712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865183712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" e1624187-e9cc-4941-981e-a77a780e1b9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865184596","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865184596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" e1624187-e9cc-4941-981e-a77a780e1b9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865184689","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865184689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" e1624187-e9cc-4941-981e-a77a780e1b9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale mfalme wa mwitu alikuwa Bwana Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865199900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865199900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865200123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865200123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865201086","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865201086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865202358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865202358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865205235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865205235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865206079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865206079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865206392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865206392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865207626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865207625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865211095","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865211095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865212078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865212078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865212331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865212330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865213273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865213273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865216085","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865216085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865217118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865217118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865217591","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865217591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865222102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865222102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549865222186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549865222186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190211_090141"," gameId":" 4a7f51e8-cab9-4aac-9ed2-47524ba1e211"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}